## AYGERIM BERDALIEVA

Bexley, Greater London | +44 7446 256 400 | berdali.aygerim9@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/aygerim-berdalieva/ | https://github.com/AnaraB | https://anara-berdalieva.co.uk/

## **Summary**

Trustworthy Junior Web Developer with over 2 years of practical experience and a strong background in customer service. Self-motivated to deliver top-notch results under tight deadlines and high standards. Known for exceptional communication, interpersonal skills, and a collaborative approach.

Seeking a Junior Developer role to leverage my technical expertise and leadership abilities.

#### **Skills**

- HTML 5, CSS 3, JavaScript
- OOP, jQuery, APIs, AJAX,
- ReactJS, TypeScript
- Bootstrap, Tailwind, Material UI
- TDD/BDD, CI/CD
- PHP, SQL, Node, MongoDB
- GitHub, GitLab
- Trello, Jira
- WordPress, Webflow

- Understanding UX/UI best practices
- Adept at Mastering New Concepts
- Knowledge in Agile Methodology
- Excellent Communication Skills
- Adaptable Team Player
- Analytical Problem Solver
- · Results Driven Collaborator
- Troubleshooting and Debugging
- Applying AI, learning Blockchain

### **Projects**

#### "Team Profile Generator" | https://github.com/AnaraB/OOP team profile generator

- Command line application that generates an HTML webpage on a software engineering team.
- User is prompted with guestions to provide information about employees.
- The assignment requirements were: all tests pass, use OOP and command line interface.
- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Inquirer, Jest, TDD, OOP, Bootstrap, Command line, Node.js

### "Gazetteer" | https://github.com/AnaraB/gazetteer | https://gazetteer.anara-berdalieva.co.uk/

- · Map-based app to provide information on countries, with a focus on a "mobile-first" development
- Provides profiling for all countries through extensive use of third party APIs. Application had to meet all assignment criteria in order to be signed off by the tutor
- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query, Bootstrap, Leaflet, PHP, AJAX, Remote API access, XAMPP

## "Company Directory" | <a href="https://github.com/AnaraB/companydirectory">https://companydirectory.anara-berdalieva.co.uk/</a>

- A "mobile-first" application to maintain a company personnel database (MySQL).
- The application allows the user to manipulate the database using simple interface which connects front-end components to server side endpoints. Application had to meet all assignment criteria in order to be signed off by the tutor
- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, MariaDB, XAMPP, phpMyAdmin

## **Experience**

# Co-Founder/Director Key Financial Services Limited

04/2021 to 04/2023 London, ENG

Organisational and communication skills

- Assisted clients with preparation for personal tax returns, submitted the clients' Confirmation Statements to Companies Houses.
- · Maintained the payroll system for clients and issued monthly payslips to the clients' employees

Childminder

#### **Anara's Childminding Services**

Interpersonal skills and multi-tasking

- Maintained detailed records for children, showcasing proficiency in record-keeping and documentation.
- Created and facilitated fun, educational activities for children.
- Worked in partnership with parents to provide appropriate care and promote the welfare of each child.
- · Completed daily risk assessments, as per the OFSTED requirements.

### Founder of gluten free catering

01/2017 to 12/2019

08/2019 to 03/2021

London, ENG

London, ENG

**Anarka's Goodness Bites** 

Creativity, multi-tasking, marketing, budgeting and communication skills

- Single-handedly baked, packaged, advertised and delivered the product to customers.
- Undertook marketing research and customer surveys to identify customer preferences
- Promoted the products in local fairs, markets and food festival.
- Created the website, brand and packaging for the products.

## Sales Assistant, Bond Street main branch Debenhams

04/2013 to 01/2017 London, ENG

Customer service skills and teamwork

• Attended to customers' needs and processed transactions efficiently, demonstrating product knowledge, professionalism and customer-centric approach.

#### **Education**

#### Front-End Web Development boot camp (use of GitBash and VSCode)

edX, London 11/2023 to 03/2024

In HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, jQuery, Node.js, React, Netlify, GitHub, Trello, Slack Average grade achieved for 14 projects covering the entire programme: 97% (of which 8 projects were completed with 100% result)

#### **Full Stack Web Development**

IT Career Switch Ltd, London

06/2022 to 08/2023

During the traineeship demonstrated a very competent level of the following programming languages and technical skills: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, AJAX, JSON, APIs, PHP, SQL, Git and GitHub, deployment. At the end of traineeship independently created two projects: Gazetteer and Company Directory

#### GCSE English Language(Grade B)

Bromley Adult Education College, UK

09/2018 to 07/2019

#### **BA International Realtions(Grade: Distinction)**

Tashkent State Institute of Oriental Studies, Uzbekistan

09/2001 to 07/2005

#### **Hobbies**

Travelling, Volunteering, Psychology, Photography, Cooking, Dog training